indbc.com 2018-06-16

# INDBC Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Last modified: 14th July 2011

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by INDBC. or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. Sometimes, we may post product specific privacy notices or Help Center materials to explain our products in more detail. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by mailing to **contact [at] indbc [dot] com**.

### What Information we collect and how we use it

We may collect the following types of information:

**Information you provide** – When you sign up for a INDBC Account, we ask you for personal information. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other INDBC services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. 

**Cookies** – When you visit INDBC, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our services, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection. INDBC also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers serve and manage ads on INDBC services.

**Log information** – When you access INDBC services via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.

**User communications** – When you send email or other communications to INDBC, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services.

**Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to INDBC services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results, sites that include INDBC applications, products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

In addition to the above, we may use the information we collect to: 

  * Provide, maintain, protect, and improve our services (including advertising services) and develop new services; and 
  * Protect the rights or property of INDBC or our users.

If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

INDBC processes personal information on our servers in INDIA and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information outside your own country.

### Choices

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some INDBC features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

### Information sharing

INDBC only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of INDBC in the following limited circumstances: 

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of INDBC, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If INDBC becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to INDBC employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

### Accessing and updating personal information

When you use INDBC services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

### Enforcement

INDBC regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is INDBC’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between INDBC and an individual. 

### Who else has access to your personal information?

The ads appearing on INDBC’s website are delivered to you by Google Adsense or our Web advertising serving partners. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. And, in the course of serving advertisements to this site, third party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. For more information about Google Adsense, cookies, and how to “opt-out”, please go to <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx>

We have also contracted with a number of advertising network partners to monitor certain pages of our website and RSS feeds for the purpose of reporting website and RSS traffic, statistics, advertisement “click-throughs,” and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, these advertising network partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to these network partners. For more information about how the information is collected and used, please see the following:

* Feedburner’s privacy policy at <http://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy>

* Google’s privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

* Statcounter’s privacy policy <http://statcounter.com/privacy.html>

Third parties and web sites that have links on our site may also collect or use information about you. The information practices of other companies or people that INDBC does not employ or manage are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).
